Login / Register
Chinese (Traditional)
Transport
Shopping
Coupons 
Travel
Online shopping
Customer service
FAQ
Logout
New member        
*Name
Last name
First name
Mobile phone number        
Please do not include symbols or spaces
Obtain verification number via mobile phone 
Phone verification number
Please enter the 6-digit verification number from your mobile phone text message        
Invitation code        
I have read and agree to the terms of service and privacy policy        
Login with Facebook                
Login with Google
or
*set password
Please enter at least 6 characters. The password is case sensitive.
Confirm password
Please enter your password again                
Confirm
Already a member? Login now
Login
Account        
Phone number or email
Password
The password is case sensitive        
Forgot your password?
Login
Not a member? Register now
Forgot your password?
Account
Phone number or email
Confirm
Phone verification number
Please enter the 6-digit verification number from your mobile phone text message                
Confirm
Resend verification number
Reset password                
New password
Please enter at least 6 characters. The password is case sensitive.
Confirm your new password
Please enter your password again        
Confirm
Product
Price (NT$)
Product details
Customer information
Name
Last name
First name
Mobile phone number
Please do not include symbols or spaces        
Terms & Conditions
I have read, understand and accept the Terms & Conditions. Eyesmedia reserve the right to accept / reject the final order.
Order now                
Billing        
Price (NT$)
Product details
LINE Pay                
Apple Pay                
Pay by credit card
Cancel
Transaction successful
Order #
Shop
Payment method
Payment amount
Return to previous page
Transaction failed        
Unfortunately, your transaction did not go through possibly due to:
Empty or invalid verification code.
The issuing bank of your credit card either does not provide NCCC installments or have enough available credit.
Please contact your issuing bank for support.
Return to previous page
Header                        
Hamburger menu        
Web logo
Footer
Eyesmedia 
Tel : +886-2-2707-8600  Address: 5F, 76 Section 2, Dunhua South Road, Da’an Dist, Taipei City
Book a ride
Pickup location: Please enter an address
Where to: Please enter an address
Book a ride        
Past booking record
Select pickup location
Please select a pickup location on the map
Select this location
Pickup location
Searching for available vehicles. Please wait for 90 seconds.
Cancel booking
Booking successful. Our driver is on the way for service.
Booking completed.
Estimated time of arrival.
Driver
Car number
Cancel booking
Confirm booking
Driver
Car number
Arriving in x minutes
Details
Date / Time
Origin
Destination
Fee (NT$)                                       
Pay
Date / Time
Origin
Destination
Service code
KRTC day pass
Purchase
KRTC two-day pass
QR code        
Validation date:
Expiry date: 
Back
Airport transfer service
Waiting for confirmation
Check your reservation
Book now
Booking number XXXXXX
Booking number XXXXXX
Back
Reservation number
Airport pickup service
Reservation status        Waiting for confirmation
Flight arrival date
Flight arrival time
Flight number
Airport / Terminal
Taoyuan International Airport, Terminal 1
Pickup date
Pickup time
Destination
Car type
2.0L Sedan
2 Adults
2 Big luggage
2 Small luggage
Back
More...
Schedules        
KRTC/KLRT map
KRTC schedule        
KLRT schedule        
THSR timetable
KRTC + iPass
Service details
Play a game and win a prize 
Default homepage        
Local area map        
Nearby places                        
All
Restaurants        
Hotels
Activities        
Shopping
Business logo                        
Shop name                        
Address                
Opening hours                                
Opening status icon
Coupons  icon
Business details                        
Shop image                        
Shop name                        
Address                
Phone #                        
Website                        
Opening hours                
Discount
Expiry date        June 30, 2019
Discount
Expiry Date        June 30, 2019
Shop info        
Coupons screen
Shop name                
Discount                
QR code
Expiry date
Terms of service                                
Shop details
Payment        
Default homepage                                
Enter keywords        
Business logo                
Shop name                        
Address                
Opening hours                                
Opening status icon                        
Coupons icon                
Coupons screen                        
Shop name                        
Discount                                
QR code
Expiry date                                
Terms of service                                
Shop info
Payment                
Shop details                                
Shop image                                
Shop name                        
Address                
Phone #                        
Website                        
Opening hours
Discount
Expiry Date        June 30, 2019
Discount
Expiry Date        June 30, 2019        
Shop info
Name
Mobile phone number
Address        
Login method
Login with account name and password
Reset
Change password
Transportation pass
X transportation passes linked                
Details
Add
Coupons 
Valid                     
Used
Expired
Transaction record                                
Change password                
Set new password
At least 6 characters. Case sensitive.
Confirm new password
Please enter your password again
Confirm
Transaction record                                
Order number                
Shop name                        
Payment method                                
Payment amount                        
Transaction status
Successful / Failed                
Transportation pass detail                
Pass info        
Edit pass        
Delete pass        
Confirm changes        
Add new transportation pass                        
Link new pass        
Customize pass name                        
iPass card number                        
Confirm                
Coupon record
Shop name                        
Discount                                
Date of use
Notification copywriting
Name: Invalid name format
Mobile phone # : Invalid mobile phone number
Email: Invalid email
Please check the box to agree with our terms of service.
You have already purchased [Plan 1]. Continue shopping?
You have already purchased [Plan 1]. Please check your email for the “Purchase successful” mail and claim your product by following the instructions in the mail.
We have sent the payment link to your email for transaction security reasons. Please check your mailbox for a “Payment notification” email and follow the instruction to complete payment. * If you have not received a “Payment notification” email, please make sure you entered the correct email address and re-submit the purchase.
Thank you for your purchase. Please check your email for the “Purchase complete” mail and claim your product by following the instructions in the mail.
Thank you for your purchase. Your coupon has been transferred to your account. You can browse available coupons in the “Coupons” section.
Welcome back
Incorrect account name or password. Please login with correct information.
This accounted is binded with a third party account. Please logon with your Google account or Facebook account.
Invalid account name. Please enter the correct information.
We have sent an email with a link to reset your password. Please check your email and follow the instruction to reset your password.
Verification code sent. Please enter the 6 digit verification code sent to your text message.
Password updated
Invalid verification code. Please enter the correct verification code.
Verification code will be available after one hour. Please check 
Phone verification completed. Please continue to finish your registration.
Name: Invalid name format
Email: Invalid email address
Membership terms and conditions : check the box to agree.
Invalid password. The password needs to include at least 6 characters. Case sensitive.
Password confirmation failed. Please enter correct information.
Successfully registered. All your purchases and coupons have been transferred to your account. You can browse your coupons in the “Coupons” section.
Successfully registered. Your coupons have been transferred to your account. You can browse your coupons in the “Coupons” section.
Please login to access member-only features.
You do not have any coupons. Purchase coupons now?
Please enter the complete address of your pickup and drop-off locations.
Sorry, there are no available drivers at the moment. Please try again later.
Before you exit the car, you may pay the amount entered by the driver.
Car fee not found. Please try again later or use the QR-code to proceed with payment.
You have booked a vehicle at xx:xx and there is no payment record at the moment. Pay now? 【I have already paid】【Pay now】
You have arrived your destination. We wish you a pleasant journey.
Airport service reservation successful
Please enable GPS positioning features to share your location.
Online shipping is available for the Taiwan region only. We do not provide shipment service overseas. We sincerely apologize for your inconvenience. 
The login method has been changed.
Online shipping is available for Taiwan only.
【 Eyesmedia 】Payment Notification
Your order has been placed. Please click on the payment link below to checkout.
Payment link
Reminder
Please proceed to checkout before 〔2019/06/17 12:00〕
 The order will be cancelled if this process is not completed by this time.
Reminder: Please proceed to checkout before 〔2019/06/17 12:00〕. The order will be cancelled if this process is not completed by this time.
LINE online customer service ｜ Contact us
【 Eyesmedia 】Purchase successful
Hi,
Thank you! Eyesmedia has received your payment
Please follow the instructions below to claim your purchase:
1. Please complete your membership registration to claim your coupons.
2. Please bring your promo code to the appointed location to claim your FunCard. *To prevent an issues claiming your FunCard due to unstable Internet connections, we suggest you save your promo code into your mobile device in advance.
Designated location:
Kaohsiung International Airport - Golden Founders travel service counter
Arrival hall. 1F, 2 Zhongshan 4th Road, Xiaogang Dist. Kaohsiung City.
Hours: AM 6:00 ~ AM 12:30
KRTC Formosa Boulevard Station
B1, 115 Zhongshan 1st Road, Xinxing Dist. Kaohsiung City.
Hours:
KRTC Cultural Center Station
B1, 45 Zhongzheng 2nd Road, Lingya Dist. Kaohsiung City.
Hours:
KRTC Kaohsiung International Airport Station
B1, 2-2 Zhongshan 4st Road, Xiaogang Dist. Kaohsiung City.
Hours:
KRTC Zuoying (THSR) Station
B1, 107 Gaotie Road, Zuoying Dist. Kaohsiung City.
Hours:
4. Important notes: 
- FunCard will be valid for 48 hours after initial use.
- Please be sure to keep good care of your FunCard. Reissues are not available in the event of loss.
LINE online customer service ｜ contact us
【 Eyesmedia 】Purchase successful
Name of customer
Thank you! Eyesmedia has received your payment of 〔NT$x,xxx〕
Please complete your membership registration to claim your coupons.
【 Eyesmedia 】Please reset your password
Please click on the link below to setup your new password:
[Link to password reset]
(If you’re unable to click on the link, please copy the link address and paste it on the URL bar of your browser).
Text message
Hello. Thank you for using Asia FunCard. Your verification code is : XXXXXX
Click on “Add to homepage” below to instantly create a shortcut to Asia FunCard.
Click on “Add to homepage” in menu to instantly create a shortcut to Asia FunCard.
